

HANH VU THI

Business Development

ABOUT ME

I am a sale specialist with 7 years of experience, spanning from factory operations to e- commerce. My expertise lies in helping clients and sellers find their products and assisting manufacturers in bringing their products online for sales on platforms such as Amazon, Etsy or Faire.

EDUCATION

HUFLIT UNIVERSITY

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

2008 - 2012

I hold a Bachelor's degree in Business Administration, which I earned after completing a four-year course of study.

EXPERIENCE

DEBION

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT

03/2022 -07/2014

- As a BD my primary responsibility is support overall business planning from working with the manufactures to R&D products, selling prices and selling plan on e-commerce platforms.
- I oversee the full project lifecycle, assisting customers in developing new products or collections, managing delivery to their warehouses, and completing payment steps.
- Developed and executed online sales strategies resulting in a 25% increase in revenue over 12 months.
- Utilized CRM tools to track customer interactions and improve customer satisfaction by 15%

TRUONG THANH (TTF)

RETAIL SPECIALIST

11/2019 - 02/2022

- My primary responsibility is to drive business growth and expansion by working closely with our partners and designers.
- I collaborate with partners to develop new business channels and identify opportunities for growth,
 while also working with designers to create new collections and develop catalogs and ODM products
- Through effective leadership and strong communication, I ensure that our retail operations are aligned with our business goals and deliver exceptional results.

MITSSY

CUSTOMER SERVICE LEADER

10/2016 - 11/2019

As a Customer Service Lead, my primary responsibility is to oversee and manage a team of customer service representatives to ensure the highest level of customer satisfaction. In addition, I am responsible for driving revenue growth by setting clear revenue targets and working with my team to achieve them. Through effective leadership and strong communication, I ensure that our team delivers exceptional customer service while meeting or exceeding our revenue goals

WALL STREET ENGLISH

EDUCATIONAL CONSULTANT

03/2016 - 10/2016

Finding out the need of students and reach their Hot

Button and tackle them effectively. Follow up the

prospects from beginning and achieved final step

CONTACT

+84 968 534 700

■ hanhvuthi12@gmail.com

Nguyen Huu Cau Street, D01, HCM

● DOB:1990